beautychoice.com 2011-10-07

# BeautyChoice.com - Privacy Policy -- Your Info is Safe

BeautyChoice.com values the users of our web site (the "Website") and their access to the services offered on it (the "Services"), and we know your privacy is important to you. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect it, and what we do with it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

 **How and when we collect information: **  
We collect "personal" information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product from us, we collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number and email address. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address. If you utilize Services or take advantage of special offers made by us or our marketing partners, we may collect other personal information about you.

 **What we do with your information:**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your e-mail address with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We use your personal information for internal purposes such as processing and keeping you informed of your order. You may, from time to time, receive information from us about new features, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you take advantage of special offers made by our marketing partners, we may transfer your personal information to them. Also, we make our customer's mailing addresses available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you.

The personal information that you give us when you place an order or utilize one of the Services is used to process and fulfill your order or request. We also use your personal information for our own internal purposes, such as providing customer support or providing, maintaining, evaluating and improving the Services and the Website. We use our customers' non-personal information to track their use of the Website and the Services and for other internal purposes. We also make our customers' non-personal information available, in aggregate form, to marketing partners, advertisers and others in order to assist us in improving our services and reaching customers with information that is relevant to them.

We partner with one or more credit card processing companies to assist us in processing your payment. However, those companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. The information you provide us is used for processing and fulfilling your order and contacting you if we have problems processing your order.

We may disclose the personal and non-personal information of our customers to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information will likely be among the assets transferred. We may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process.

 **Your choice to opt-out of certain communications:**  
If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, please e-mail your request to [csupport@BeautyChoice.com](mailto:csupport@BeautyChoice.com) . Please include your complete name and mailing address (as well as your e-mail address) if you prefer not to receive direct mail postcards or catalogs. Note that you may still receive customer service related communications from us.

 **We link to other sites:**  
This Website may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

 **IP address and cookies:  
** We also collect "non-personal" information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP address. "Non-personal" information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the site. 

In addition, like almost all e-commerce web sites, we use "cookies." Cookies are bits of information that are stored on your computer by your web browser. Although our cookies don't store any of your personal information, they do allow us to do things like keep items in your shopping cart between visits or during the same visit or provide you with a more personalized user experience. Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. 

We may collect and share non-personal information about the pages that you visit on the Website, but this information is not personally identifiable, and we may use selected third parties for marketing and analysis purposes.

 **How we protect your information:**   
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us from unauthorized access or disclosure, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Other than our limited security guarantee, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

 **Children's Privacy:  
** The Services are intended for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13. Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Services under their parents' or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we delete any of your personal information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us at: [csupport@BeautyChoice.com](mailto:csupport@BeautyChoice.com).

**Updating your personal information:**  
If your personal information changes, you may correct, update or remove personal information previously provided to us by contacting our customer service department at [](mailto:Support@Art.Com)[csupport@BeautyChoice.com](mailto:csupport@BeautyChoice.com). 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**  
If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a new Privacy Policy on our Website, which will become effective when posted. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of the Website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent with it. 

**Contact us:**  
If you ever have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at [csupport@BeautyChoice.com](mailto:csupport@BeautyChoice.com).
